

Applicant for:

Web Backend Developer (Java) ~\$1800

Dr.JOY 9 June 2020

nguyen duc long

✓ nguyenduclong02@gmail.com

Main interests: Java, Team Leader

What skills, work projects or achievements make you a strong candidate for this position?

I'm a full-stack developer with 9 years of experience. I've been working as a team leader for 4 years. I'm familiar with Spring, Angular JS.



Nguyen Duc Long

Date of birth: Nov 02, 1986

Gender: Male

Phone: 0986739963

Email: nguyenduclong02@gmail.com

Address: Tran Cung, Co Nhue, Tu Liem, Hanoi, Vietnam

OBJECTIVE

Looking for a job as a software engineer at a company where I can work with new technologies and the international environment. Contribute my experience and knowledge to develop the applications as a developer and a leader.

EDUCATION

Sep 2005 - Aug 2010 Ha Noi University of Science and Technology

Major: Information Systems

SKILLS

PROGRAMMING Angular JS, Angular, React, Vue JS

Spring, Struts, JSF

Cassandra, Oracle, MySQL, MongoDB Junit Test, Robot Framework, Cypress

Sonar, Nexus, Maven Docker, GitLab CI/CD

LANGUAGE English

Vietnamese(native)

WORK EXPERIENCE

Aug 2015 – Present

IFI Solution

Role: Developer, Team Leader

Main responsibilities:

- Develop Front-End and Back-End for web application in Energy Management.
- Communicate with customers to know their needs therefore contribute to make requirement clearer.
- Manage as team leader to ensure product meet customer expectation in both quality and deadline.

Mar 2012 - May 2015 Viettel Group

Role: Developer

Main responsibilities:

- Develop Back-End for web application in Finance and ERP.

- Support customer issues and provide assistance if needed

- Provide solutions in developing features.

Role: Developer Main responsibilities:

- Develop Back-End for web application in e-commerce field

Write test cases and Junit test.

PROJECTS

DTAG

(2020 - present)

Customer	NTT Data Germany
Description	A web application to ordering subscriptions and devices of a telecom company
Team size	5
My position	Developer
My responsibilities	 Responsible for understanding the technologies used by customers Communicate with customers about technical and business issues Developing back-end functions and also take part in developing front-end if necessary
Technologies used	- Spring - Vue JS, Cypress - Zeebe, Open API - MongoDB

Portal Standard

(2018 - 2020)

	(10.0 10.0)	
Customer	Energisme	
Description	Web application to manage energy consumption.	
Team size	7	
My position	Team Leader	
My responsibilities	 Talk with customers to understand customer's needs Communicate and give advice to customers to make requirements clearer Provide technical solutions if needed Manage the progress of team Review code Manage the script CD to deploy automatically 	

Technologies used	Struts, SpringAngular JSJBoss Application ServerGitLab CI/CD
-------------------	---

E2XTool

(2018 - 2018)

Customer	NTTData Japan
Description	Web Application to train data for some models that use to recognize images
Team size	4
My position	Front-End Developer
My responsibilities	- Develop UI of web application - Deploy the application
Technologies used	- Angular 6 - Apache

Lab of Energy

(2015 - 2017)

(2010-2011)	
Customer	Energisme
Description	A project that makes demonstration of features for Energy management application
Team size	5
My position	Developer, Team Leader
My responsibilities	 Communicate with customer. Analysis and design Provide technical solutions if needed Development
Technologies used	- Struts, Spring boot - Cassandra - JQuery, CSS - MySQL - ActiveMQ

Finance System of Viettel

(2013 - 2015)

Customer	Viettel Group
Description	Web application to manage Finance System of Group
Team size	10
My position	Back-End Developer

My responsibilities	- Create processes to synchronize data from other systems - Create some feature to manage: good, charge, revenue - Provide technical solutions if needed - Support customer issues and provide assistance if needed
Technologies used	- Adempiere - Oracle DB

Internal Management

(2012 - 2013)

	(
Customer	Viettel Group	
Description	Web application to manage Tasks, Customers	
Team size	4	
My position	Developer	
My responsibilities	- Analysis and Design - Develop web application	
Technologies used	- JSF - MySQL	

EMC

(2010 - 2012)

Customer	A Japanese Company
Description	An e-commerce web application
Team size	20
My position	Developer
My responsibilities	Write test casesDevelop Back-EndCreate the unit test
Technologies used	- Java - Struts - Oracle

EXPECTED SALARY

NET \$1500

INTERESTS

- Outdoor activities such as football, Camping, swimming...